Welcome to Pacific Sodium Technologies
Turning Salt Into Power — The Next Energy Revolution Begins at the Salton Sea
Why Sodium Beats Lithium
Fire-safe. Non-toxic. Heat-stable. No cobalt. 1000x more abundant than lithium.
Modular Closed-Loop Factory
Brine In → Sodium Extraction → Cell Manufacturing → Reinjection
Environmental Commitment
100% Brine Reinjection. Zero Freshwater Use. Transparent Public Dashboard.
The $1 Trillion Market Opportunity
EVs, grid storage, off-grid power. IRA-aligned U.S. battery independence.
How We Make Money
Sodium sales, battery sales, licensing tech, environmental credits.
Execution Timeline
2025: Filing → 2026: MVP Factory → 2027: Partnerships → 2028: National Scale
Team & Technology
Field-tested builders. Fire-safe IP. Closed-loop sodium cell system.
Join the Revolution
Seeking collaborators, grant partners, and industry allies.
The Future Is Salt
Pacific Sodium Technologies – Forged in Geothermal Heat, Powered by American Salt